Coming back to the new chat, I will be able to create and start a new conversation, a brand new conversation, and this time, I want to use another option of chat GPT.
So I want to ask chat GPT to, for example, shape me an image, right?
So I wanted to, let's go to this local research request actually and continue our conversation over here, right?
So I want to say that I provided you with a logo of the take-off college.
This time, I want you to redesign the logo and create me a brand new one for the same exact brand, right?
So this time, we're asking chat GPT to generate us some media, generate us images.
So as you know, in this very course, we also have specific and special tools when it comes to image generation, and chat GPT is not one of them tools, but chat GPT as a chat bot also provides us with the ability to generate images.
So by clicking on this create image option, I will be able to change my command to an image creation command, and by clicking send, it also has a context of the logo, and if I wait a little bit, I will get my image created.
So it says creating image, the take-off college logo redesign.
So as you see, it says image created, and if we wait a couple seconds, we will be able to see the end result.
Yes, so as you see, this is what we got the take-off college. This is the redesign that chat GPT provided us with. So I don't think if this one is better than the logo that we already have, but whatever, this is what chat GPT created, right?
So this is an image generated by AI, and this is another option that we turned on using this create image option, and we're able to share it. We're able to download it by clicking this button over here, you know, and they are all doable.